All the CSC Valley who have passed the Finance and
R&P exams and have activated the
insurance service on their digital service portal,
such as - after passing the exam they have
activated the insurance service
or after passing the live exam they have
activated the insurance service on their digital service portal, then
how can they download their - or R&P certificate, I am going to
show you the complete method of this,
friend I will
download both the certificates and show you how to
download the - certificate and
how to download the R&P certificate,
so let's start the video, so
first of all we have opened a website, this is the
new website of CSC, although this
website was launched about one and a half to two months or three
months ago, from here anyone
can give the Celebrity Sinus and R&P exam, can
register and activate
all the insurance services on their digital service portal,
so we had registered for both - and R&P,
both the exams were cleared
and the certificates of both have come,
so first of all we will
show you how to download the R&P certificate,
after that we will also show you how to download the - certificate,
so here you
can see the details of this website  You will
find the link in the description. After this, to
download the RAP certificate from here, we will
open the RAP option given here. After this, we will come down and
click on login. After this, you have to
enter your CSC ID and password and
click on sign in. After this, you
can see that our RAP dress vote has
opened and from here we will
download the RAP certificate and
show it to you. We have also passed the RAP exam
and our certificate has also been generated, which we will
download and
show to you. So here below you can see the
certificate option is given.
We will click on it to download the certificate.
After this,
you can see that your certificate has been generated here.
IRDA certificate or RAP certificate,
both are called this certificate. RAP
certificate or IRDA certificate. To
download this certificate, we will
come down and below here you can see the
option of generate certificate is given.
Click on it and here you can see that
this certificate has been downloaded and
we will open this certificate and
show it to you. Click on this shoulder
and this  The certificate has been downloaded. Let's
open it and show it to you.
We have downloaded our RAP certificate, which is also called the IRDA certificate. In
this way, you
can also download your RAP certificate.
After this, let's show you
how to download your RAP certificate if you have given the exam for -. So,
first of all, we will log out of it.
To download the RAP certificate, we have used the
login option for RAP. We will log out of it
and here you can see that we are back
on the main page. Now we will also show you
how to download the RAP certificate.
Here you can see, first we will
run our key here. We will come down and
click on login. After this, we will enter our
CSC ID and password and log in.
Here you can see that we have logged in.
After this, we will come down again to the
certificate option and
click here to download this certificate.
Here you can see that our
certificate has been generated.
This certificate is the certificate of -. From here,
we will download the - certificate and
show it to you. We will come down to download it.
And again we will click on generate certificate here
and here you can see that
this certificate has been downloaded, let us
open this video and show it to you people
and here you can see that
we have downloaded this certificate,
you will get to see this incident like this,
in this you will see one thing different,
in the rap certificate which is difficult to
download, there is
no photo of any kind in it, it is
of Valley and in this certificate, the photo of Valley is there,
so here you can see that
if you have passed the exam of Re Piya and have
activated both the services on your digital service portal, then in this way you
can download the certificate of Rap Fans,
so we hope that you people would have
liked the information in this video and
you people would have liked the video, if you like the video then
like the video, if you have come to our channel for the
first time then do subscribe to the channel
so that
you keep getting notifications of such upcoming update videos, till then
thank you in the next video